Keith Black

Denver, Colorado 80231 (845) 625-9783

Keithblack4290@gmail.com

LinkedIn: /kblack4290 Portfolio: kblack4290.github.com GitHub:/kblack4290

Objective

Hard-working individual with proficiency in HTML, JavaScript, and CSS, as well as ability to communicate effectively in a team setting, and possessing a strong willingness to learn from an experienced team as a Junior Web Developer.

Areas of Strength

Communication • Adaptability • Problem Resolution
Critical Thinking • Creativity
Customer Service • Learning Agility • Analytical Abilities
Dependability • Client and Customer Retention • Leadership

Technical Skills

Languages: JavaScript ES6+, CSS3, HTML5

Applications: GitHub, GitLab, Virtual Studio Code, GitBash

Tools: Node, Query, Bootstap, Foundation, Various API's, Postman

Projects

Concoctions | github.com/glchavez/Project-One | github.com/glchavez/Project-One

- Summary: An application that provides recipes
- Role: Html, CSS, and assisted JavaScript
- Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Foundation, API's

Workday Planner | github.com/Kblack4290/Work-Day-Planner | kblack4290.github.io/Work-Day-Planner/

- Summary: A day planner to help the user organize their day
- Role: Sole author
- Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Google Fonts, Moments API

$Password\ Generator\ |\ \underline{github.com/Kblack4290/Password\text{-}Generator}\ |\ \underline{kblack4290.github.io/Password\text{-}Generator/}$

- Summary: An application that generates a random password between 8-128 characters
- Role: Sole author
- Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Education and Certification

Bachelor of Science 2013

Major: History Minor: Business Administration State University of New York at Plattsburgh

Plattsburgh, New York

Full Stack Flex Course December 2020-June 2021

University of Denver (https://bootcamp.du.edu/coding/)

Trilogy Education Services

Denver, Colorado

Experience

Cornerstone Apartment Services, Denver, Colorado

October 2017 – Present

Portfolio Manager

- Manage 335 Apartments in various properties from small multifamily homes to large apartment buildings totaling over \$50,000,000 in assets
- Manage a team of maintenance technicians and oversee completed maintenance work to ensure the quality and service to residents
- Service and prioritize resident's maintenance requests
- Conduct negotiations and create relationships with third party vendors
- Maintain quality resident relations and customer service
- Implement resident retention strategies
- Weekly meetings with leasing to brainstorm, organize, and implement leasing strategies
- Meet with investors and clients to review property goals and improvements
- Effectively reduce delinquency to increase NOI
- Optimize rental income and improve curb appeal
- Develop and oversee the budget and financial reports to maximize profitability
- Consistently reach monthly budget and collection goals
- Maintain monthly budget and prepare bonus summaries, month end reports and leasing summaries
- Oversee and control Capital Expenditure Projects to meet or exceed budget expectations

eBay, Beacon, New York

April 2016 – January 2020

Online Retailer

- Created, marketed, and managed successful online retail business with over \$3,000 per month in sales
- Responsible for all bookkeeping, shipping, public relations, purchasing and quality assurance
- Promote business through social media sites, Facebook, and Pinterest
- Efficiently managed inventory of over 500 items with constant flow of units into and out of storage area.
- Able to satisfy multiple client orders and maintain excellent feedback rating of over 99%

Emery & Webb Insurance, Fishkill, New York

January 2015 – January 2017

Business Development Representative (2016-2017)

Client Service Representative (2015-2016)

- Responsible for developing, managing, and organizing sales
- Developed and maintained prospect & client relationships
- Made 100 daily outbound cold calls to prospects
- Produced mass marketing emails detailing new promotions and services using Outlook and MailChimp
- Generated and qualified prospective leads to build up our sales department pipeline
- Scheduled sales appointments for producers in their specific territories
- Organized paperwork and computer data in prospect file for future reference.
- Researched new developments in marketing and technology that could apply to company's strategy
- Reviewed, edited, and processed clients' insurance policy and account information.
- Invoiced clients' insurance packages and co-payments
- Managed, updated, and utilized company's social media accounts for marketing purposes
- Consistently met team quarterly and annual sales goals (\$2,000,000 in premiums annually)

Computer Skills

Microsoft Office – Excel, Outlook, Word, Power Point and Publisher • Google Suite – Gmail, Drive, Docs, Sheets and Meet • VS Code • GitHub • GitLab • Git Bash • Postman • Bootstrap • JavaScript • JQuery • API • CSS • HTML • DocuSign • Adobe • Yardi • OneSite